

CONTACT

- +353 83 171 0665
- ☑ ncardozo2017@gmail.com
- Apartment 99, The Academy, Park West Pointe, Park West, Dublin 12, D12 DY06

EDUCATION

2015 H.S.S.C

Fr. Basilio Andrade Memorial higher secondary school Goa Board

2013 S.S.C

St.Anthony high school Goa Board

SKILLS

- Relationship Building
- Communication skills
- Adaptability
- Detail oriented
- Sales Techniques
- Team work

LANGUAGES

- English (Fluent)
- Hindi (Fluent)
- Konkani (Fluent)

NASHWIN CARDOZO

PROFILE

I am looking forward for a challenging career opportunity where my related experiences can be utilized, applied and be a part of a progressive and highly dynamic performing organization and be able to share my skills and abilities in promoting excellence in quality service.

WORK EXPERIENCE

MARTINS CORNER BAR AND RESTUARANT

17/09/2022 - 2/05/2024

Waiter

- · Greet customers and hand out menus.
- Make menu recommendations and inform patrons of any specials.
- Deliver meals and beverages to tables when they have been prepared

P&OCRUISE LINE

17/09/2017 - 25/04/2019

Hotel Assistant

- Greeted and welcomed guests with warmth and hospitality.
- Provided attentive service by escorting guests to their tables and engaging in friendly conversation.
- Maintained strict adherence to safety and hygiene standards at all times.
- Previous experience as a Hotel Assistant, demonstrating expertise in guest service and satisfaction.
- Collaborated effectively as a bar side assistant, ensuring seamless service delivery and guest satisfaction.

HERITAGE VILLAGE AND SPA

01/07/2015 - 09/01/2016

Waiter

- Prepare the bill for tables when requested.
- Cash up bills and ensure that the correct amount has been paid.
- · Administer change to tables if needed.
- Collaborate with catering staff to ensure that tables are cleared, cleaned and waiting for the next party.